Downloaded @ subs4free.club
[CREATURES SQUEALING]
[HISSING, SNARLING]
I am Knull.
God of the void.
Slicer of worlds.
Long ago,
when light invaded my kingdom,
my symbiote children betrayed me
and imprisoned me here.
At last,
a codex has been created.
It is the key to my freedom.
It will unlock this prison.
I order you to search
the corners of the universe
until you find this key.
Find me the codex.
[GROWLING]
[CODEX PULSING]
[GROWLS]
And when I escape,
and annihilate
every living planet
and destroy
my symbiote offspring,
I will reward you...
with your lives.
[CHITTERING]
[PORTALS PULSATE]
[LATIN AMERICAN MUSIC PLAYING]
EDDIE: So you're saying
in this universe,
there's these superhero people.
All right.
So tell me again
about your purple alien friend
who really loves stones.
'Cause I'll tell you what, man,
aliens, they do not love stones.
- VENOM: Eddie, don't start.
- No.
No, they do not love stones.
Do you know what they love?
They love eating brains!
Because that's what they do.
Señor, he made
my family disappear.
For five years.
Five years, huh?
Well, that is a long time.
All right.
VENOM: Eddie!
We are drunk!
- [VENOM BURPS]
- [PORTAL PULSATES]
[EDDIE SCREAMS]
VENOM: We're home!
I'm so done
with the multi-verse shit.
And I like our version
of the barman better.
Ow. My head hurts.
I feel like I'm drunk,
but I'm also hungover
at the same time.
VENOM: Eddie!
You want a Bloody María.
Oh yeah!
[VENOM HUMS BACKGROUND SONG]
- No.
- I don't want a drink.
[CONTINUES HUMMING]
Stop! You are destroying
this man's bar!
VENOM: Tequila!
I'm having the time
of my life, Eddie!
I'd rather have
a glass of water.
VENOM: Be a man, Eddie.
We should've been a bartender!
- Tequila!
- I did it.
VENOM: I did it.
What the hell were those things?
I was born with them.
Freaking bar!
I'm done with this shit!
- [EDDIE SIGHS]
- [NEWS JINGLE PLAYING]
This is Kelly Roulet
reporting from San Francisco.
Police are still
trying to locate
former reporter
Eddie Brock for questioning...
Oh no.
...after the tragic death
of Detective Patrick Mulligan.
No.
Detective Mulligan
was found impaled
amidst a series
of bizarre happenings
at the city's cathedral.
They think that I killed him.
How long can he
evade authorities?
Only time will tell.
VENOM: If we are
on the news here,
we are on the news everywhere.
Well, we can't go back
to San Francisco.
And I'm not staying down here,
hiding for the rest of my life
in Mexico, that's for sure.
VENOM: Where will we go?
I don't know. I don't know.
Ooh.
That could work. Hey.
This judge got me
- kicked out of New York.
- VENOM: What a dick!
Yeah, I still got a ton
of shit on him too.
VENOM: I've always wanted
to see the Statue of Liberty.
Maybe we could blackmail him.
And clear my name.
VENOM: Let's go!
- Road trip!
- Let's get the hell out of here.
VENOM: Keep the change!
- [GROANS]
- [SIGN CRACKLING]
We keep our heads down,
and we keep moving.
VENOM: We are fugitives!
We are on the run!
Yes, we are innocent. Yes.
But I will eat every bad guy
that gets in our way.
I need a Tylenol.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[INDISTINCT CHITTERING]
[HOWLING]
Do you hear that?
[VENOM GRUNTS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[DISTANT SCREAMS]
VENOM: Someone's in trouble.
And I need fuel for the road.
Yeah, okay.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
VENOM: That way.
Bad men, Eddie.
Are we the Lethal Protector,
or not?
Do your thing.
VENOM: Easy-peasy.
Jesus.
[BARKING]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
VENOM: Cute!
I promise not to eat it.
They're fighting dogs.
VENOM: I draw the line
at fighting dogs, pal.
[MAN WHISTLING]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH] Oye, vato,
you're in the wrong place.
Oh, hello.
This is our territory.
Well, I assume
by the threatening look
on your faces
that I oughta be scared, right?
But you took
the wrong path, hermano.
We can't let you leave.
I have a headache
on account of the fact
that I was drinking a lot.
I'm gonna be honest.
I have a really dark
and unpredictable side to me.
We all have monsters inside us.
Not like this.
So dark that it is highly likely
to tear your head off
and feed it
to your asshole.
VENOM: Or me!
You can feed it to me!
Yeah, or I can feed it to him.
All right. Look. Whoa, whoa.
Come on. I got a suggestion.
No. Stop speaking.
I'm not gonna stop speaking.
This is for you.
I'm doing this
for your benefit, all right?
I don't have to. Okay?
So pay attention.
We're gonna find all of these
dogs loving forever homes
because what you're doing
is reprehensible.
What does your mother
think of you, man?
My mother's dead, culero.
VENOM: You made it awkward!
I'm sorry to hear that.
[CONTINUES IN SPANISH] Huh?
I'm giving you a chance.
Sweetie, I really am
giving you a chance.
You should probably take it.
VENOM: Say when.
When.
[GROANS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Hola, bitches.
[HOWLING]
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [SCREAMS]
Oh!
Who's a bad boy?
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [MAN SCREAMING]
VENOM: Now that's
some sturdy footwear!
[SCREAMING]
- [GASPS]
- Where you going?
Home. [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Nah.
[ALL SCREAMING]
What...
are you?
We are...
We are Venom!
- Venom!
- No!
- Oh!
- Yeah.
- We...
are Venom.
What?
[WHISPERS] We are totally gonna
need to work on that.
[GROWLS]
VENOM: That was delicious!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
VENOM: You take me
to all the finest places!
Let's get the hell out of here.
Where's my shoe?
Oh, hey, buddy!
That's my shoe!
That's my shoe. That's my shoe!
Give me my shoe.
[WHIMPERING]
VENOM: These will fit.
Now we are on the run
for something
we actually did do.
And I got stuck with a superhero
who can't fly.
VENOM: Wanna bet?
[CHITTERING]
[DOG BARKS DISTANTLY]
[CONTINUES CHITTERING]
MAN: There you are.
Get me General Strickland.
What the...?
[VIAL ZAPS]
Viral shedding.
These things wanna live.
Tell me about the man
who was just here.
He was acting, like, crazy.
Talking to himself.
What was he saying?
He had these big,
massive, wild arms.
They were bobbling like this.
Bring him.
- [ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
- [GROANING]
GIRL: You think there are
another brother and sister
on one of those stars...
looking at the same sky?
I'll be able to tell you
one day.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [GROANS SOFTLY]
My twin brother...
a future NASA scientist.
One day.
When thunder roars,
head indoors.
[GROANS]
No!
[GRUNTS]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES,
CHIMES]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
SOLDIER 1: He's on life support.
SOLDIER 2: Get him
to emergency symbiosis now.
It should be you.
REPORTER: This just came across
our news desk
and it bears repeating:
For all of you alien enthusiasts
out there, it's a sad day.
Washington has finally announced
the decommissioning of Area 51.
The controversial site is famous
for its alleged testing
on aliens.
In other news today...
Right this way. Come on up.
Strickland.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Strickland authorized.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
- It's finally happening, then.
- Yeah.
Yes, ma'am. Be nothing left
but rock and dust.
And roaches.
Even the biggest of bangs
couldn't kill 'em.
They've been around 280 million
years. And counting.
I did not know that, Dr. Paine.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Good to go.
- Have a good one, Gus.
- You too.
- Thank you.
- Yes, ma'am.
Morning, Dr. Paine,
we'll keep 'em safe for you.
I still don't think anyone
wants my old beater, Jim.
Never judge a book by its cover.
[DR. PAINE CHUCKLES]
Early morning wake-up,
General Strickland.
Looks like
all your dreams came true.
I know how that must bug you.
He arrived shortly
before you did.
Did our new friend
give him any trouble?
You see,
that's exactly the problem.
What?
Your assumption
we're meeting friends.
- Morning.
- [WOMAN] Good morning.
The bonding was successful.
I heard.
You always have this
look on your face
like something terrible
is imminent.
Because in my line of work
something terrible
is always imminent.
We contain them, you study them.
It's how it works.
DR. PAINE: Let's have a look.
- Hello, doctor.
- Morning.
His other symbiote
left him for dead.
We saved him.
He would have died.
Oh, try lowering those levels.
Morning, Sadie.
SADIE: Let me get that.
FORREST:
We got this down in Mexico.
Hi. Welcome.
Any more on
where the rest of him is?
- We're gettin' there.
- Update me as you have it.
I don't get this obsession.
I told you.
My mom made me this pin.
It's July.
- I'll see you in there.
- DR. PAINE: Mm-mm.
Everyone on this side...
is weird.
Leave her alone, Rex.
God forbid anyone should
actually enjoy their work.
[RUMBLING]
Area 51 will be
fully decommissioned
by the end of the week.
It's just a shipwreck anyway,
and they're tired
of the tourists.
But we don't exist down here.
A hundred feet subsurface...
undetectable to any human...
or nonhuman.
No one's phoning home from here.
My brother's greatest ambition
was to work up there at 51
doing what I do.
And I wish
I could have shown him
what we've built down here.
[PANTING]
SADIE: You're okay.
Just...
try to breathe. Okay?
DR. PAINE: When my brother
and I were kids
they told us that UFOs were just
weather balloons, space trash.
Kubrick directed the moon
landing in a Hollywood studio.
Cool story.
Where are you going? This first.
Is there an increased risk
of exposure?
It's not us I'm worried about.
You know we carry all kinds
of viruses and bacteria
that could be harmful
to a sensitive lifeform.
And we don't know exactly
what we're dealing with here.
As long as we're keeping
the guests safe.
This is the first time
we've had a host
compatible with
one of our symbiotes.
And now we'll be able
to talk to one.
Monsters.
He's been experiencing panic
surges since we bonded him.
You try "Jingle Bells"?
So soothing.
Wow, why didn't I think of that?
Release him.
Monsters.
I'm Dr. Paine. Teddy.
You're safe here.
We're gonna help you.
Both of you.
The transfer was successful.
We had no choice.
We had to try and save you.
Monsters.
You're broken too.
May I...?
May I ask you some questions?
Is the symbiote
communicating with you?
Do you hear it?
[HIGH-PITCHED FEEDBACK]
Sound distresses them.
Okay.
- Why are they here?
- What do they want?
Safe haven.
Safe haven?
We were running.
Is he talking
about the other symbiotes?
I think so.
His creatures
search the universe for us.
But we will be found.
And when we are,
he will kill us all.
Who?
There will be nothing left.
Here? On Earth?
Why were they running?
Because there is a dark,
cold sea
around this universe.
What is it?
[GROWLS, ECHOES]
You don't wanna know.
[HIGH-PITCHED FEEDBACK]
[SCREAMS]
MULLIGAN: I've seen the future.
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
[RHYTHMIC WHIRRING]
[RUMBLING]
[SPEAKING SYMBIOTE-LIKE]
The darkness
has teeth.
This is your captain speaking.
We are currently cruising
at a comfortable 31,000 feet.
If you look out there
to your left just now,
you'll see the Grand Canyon.
[SCREAMS]
VENOM: Told you we could fly.
Oh my God!
VENOM: Direct to New York.
My mouth is so dry!
VENOM: And we clear your name.
It's so unpleasantly cold!
How does Tom Cruise do this?
VENOM: He doesn't whine
like a little bitch!
[GROWLS]
[HOWLS]
[CODEX PULSING]
[ALL SCREAM]
EDDIE: What was that?
What is that?
Oh fuck!
[SCREAMS]
[VENOM SCREAMS]
I'm sorry, Eddie,
but I got to disappear.
- What, now?
- VENOM: We're in deep shit!
[EDDIE SCREAMING]
Why did you do that?
VENOM: I will explain.
No! No!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
I'm gonna go ahead and say that
this is the shittest hangover
of all time.
VENOM: Look at it, Eddie.
Isn't it just astonishing?
Oh, shut up.
VENOM: I don't think
I mind living here forever.
EDDIE: We just came face-to-face
with a literal death machine.
Forever seems pretty optimistic.
MAN: [OVER RADIO] With the
decommissioning of Area 51,
will the Pentagon finally admit
that they've been holding UAPs?
That's "unidentified aerial
phenomena" to you.
Yeah, Dad, we know.
What I wouldn't give to see
who built one of those things.
That's why we cashed in
our savings
and came on this
road trip, babe.
So you could finally
get to see--
That it's bullshit?
Yeah, well, what if I'm right?
Then I really hope
we don't end up
in an alien space lab
with probes up our asses.
- [LAUGHS]
- Or dead.
"Asses."
[PARENTS LAUGH]
- Whoa!
- NOVA: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Kicked up some gravel there.
- Hang tight, family.
- You good?
That was wild!
- Did the dog vomit?
- Yeah.
[PANTING]
[SNARLING]
[ROARS]
VENOM: Okay!
We've got this.
Soft landing. Bend your knees.
Engage your core.
Engage your core!
Yes! Yes, that's it!
Yes. That's it!
EDDIE: Whoa! [EXHALES SHARPLY]
VENOM: Well done.
That was terrifying.
Uh, this is not New York.
No, this is a wasteland.
VENOM: I'm detecting
passive aggression.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry. How about
some active aggression?
You just threw me off a 757
without even
the slightest consideration
for my chronic vertigo.
It was an Airbus A320.
Was it? I am sorry. All right.
And what was that thing?
That thing
that we just juiced back there?
You're not going to like this.
No, I can absolutely guarantee
you that I'm not gonna.
[MUTED GROANS]
What are you doing?
Why are you doing that?
That's er... You're being weird.
That's creepy.
That was a Xenophage.
A what?
A Xenophage.
- A symbiote hunter.
- Of course.
Problem is, if she has found
her way here,
others will soon follow.
"Others"?
The Xenophage's maker
also created us symbiotes.
So that's your sister.
All the symbiotes turned on him,
locked him up on Klyntar.
- Your planet.
- No!
- Not a planet.
- Not your planet.
A prison we built for him
to sleep...
- Of course.
- ...for eternity!
What's his name, then?
[MUMBLES]
I didn't hear a word you said.
Knull.
- Knull.
- No!
Shush, shush, shush, shush.
This is serious, Eddie.
Let's just not talk.
[WHIMPERING]
Quiet.
What does this
Xyla-Xyn-Xyn-thingy,
this symbiote hunter,
want with you anyway?
VENOM: It doesn't. It wants us.
We have something it needs.
We only have this shitty shirt,
we got one boot and sunburn.
And the codex.
The what, now?
I'll show you.
[GROANS]
Damn it, what are you doing?
VENOM: Let's say you died.
I could bring you back to life.
EDDIE: Well, I like that.
VENOM: But if I did,
our separate life forces
would become one single force
called a codex.
EDDIE: What the hell is a codex?
VENOM: It's a key.
A key that unlocks a cage.
EDDIE: The prison on Klyntar.
VENOM: It would
free our creator.
Well, thank God we haven't died.
VENOM: Yeah,
except that one time.
[VIBRATING]
EDDIE: Oh, no. No.
So you're telling me
we're carrying this thing.
VENOM: That's why the Xenophage
is hunting us.
[GROWLS]
EDDIE: What do we do?
VENOM: She can
only see the codex
when a symbiote
is in its full true form.
[CODEX PULSING]
Right.
You mean you can't come out?
I can do this. I can do this.
But if I fully transform,
the codex sends her
a tracking signal.
She'll find us,
rip it out of our spine
and free Knull from Klyntar.
So how do we
get rid of this codex?
As long as you and I both live,
the codex exists.
- If one of us should die...
- No.
...the codex would die.
- That's not gonna work for me.
- Nor me!
That Xenophage was fast.
It won't take long
for the feds to tie us
to those four headless bodies
we left in Mexico.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Yeah, we better go.
[PANTING]
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- Ah!
VENOM: Four legs
are better than one.
Be honest with me, buddy.
How fast do you think
you can get that thing to go?
Without killing it.
VENOM: Only one way to find out.
[VENOM SNIFFS]
Don't scare him.
Don't scare horsey-horsey-horse.
Nice horsey.
Hey.
Surprise, horsey!
[GARBLED NEIGHS]
I love horsey!
[ROARING NEIGH]
Oh! [GRUNTS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROARING NEIGH]
Let's go. Whoa!
[EDDIE SCREAMS]
VENOM: Yeehaw!
[CONTINUES SCREAMING]
VENOM: Ride me, cowboy!
You are an asshole!
I swear to God,
when I get off this horse,
I'm gonna kick your ass,
you mother-- [SCREAMS]
[EDDIE WHOOPING]
VENOM: Now that's horsepower!
STRICKLAND: Safe haven?
No. They're not here
for a safe haven.
How about a new home?
Evict the current tenants.
I think you've watched too many
alien invasion movies, Rex.
Have I?
[STRICKLAND SIGHS]
They were running.
That's what he said.
STRICKLAND: Don't kid yourself.
They were always migrating.
A meteor carrying symbiote life
crashes on Earth,
and they all survive.
Coincidence?
Give me a break.
All right.
Let's go get 'em.
You're so desperate to believe
that they're here
for altruistic reasons.
Makes you dangerous.
We just intercepted
an emergency call
from an Airbus out of Mexico
saying a man jumped
off the plane over Sequoia.
We'll take the Osprey.
Eyes wide, Paine.
[TREES THUDDING,
EDDIE SCREAMING]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[EDDIE PANTS]
I can't feel my balls.
- That...
- [DISTANT TILTROTOR]
That was horrible.
[RIFLE CHARGES, FIRES]
- [SONIC INTERFERENCE]
- [SCREAMING, NEIGHING]
[GASPING]
MAN: [OVER RADIO]
Visual on suspect.
Take him out.
- Collect the symbiote.
- Team Six engaged.
Disengage harness. Let's go.
[PROPULSOR WHIRRING]
[MUFFLED THUDS]
[MUFFLED GROANS]
[GASPS]
[CHARGES, PULSES]
[MUFFLED GROAN]
[MUFFLED GUNFIRE]
[HEART THUMPS]
[GASPS]
[BREATH TREMBLING, GROANS]
[PANTS]
[PROPULSOR WHIRRING]
[VENOM CHITTERS]
[GROWLS, CROAKS]
Oh!
Oh.
EDDIE: No! The codex!
Can't let you die.
[CHITTERS]
[VENOM SCREAMS]
[CODEX PULSING]
- [GROWLS]
- [BATON CHARGES]
[BOTH SCREAM]
[ROARING]
Where did that come from?
[CODEX PULSING]
- EDDIE: Morph!
- VENOM: Copy.
- [ROARS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- VENOM: Time to go!
- EDDIE: Hell yeah!
[MUFFLED FIRING]
[GRUNTS. ROARS]
[SOLDIERS SCREAM]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[SOLDIERS CONTINUE SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
[CHITTERING, HOWLS]
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
What happened?
There's something else out here.
- Something else?
- He said this would happen.
I just lost three people.
Can you collect any samples?
Samples?
[PANTING]
Those were not feds.
Those were some
special forces shit.
VENOM: They were
trying to kill us.
EDDIE: Yeah.
Yeah, great. Great.
So now we have the cops,
the United States Army
and some creature
from hell hunting us.
Oh, God, I just saw
blood mist spray
out of the back
of an alien's face.
I killed someone.
VENOM: They didn't
give you a choice.
You didn't give me a choice.
VENOM: I couldn't get to you.
Not in the rapids. A year ago
when you stole my life.
VENOM: We've been together
for a whole year?
A year too long.
Just stay hidden
while we get to New York
without getting killed.
[LOCK PINGING]
[POWERING DOWN]
PAINE: We need you to come out.
The thing you talked about,
the creature...
It's here.
It killed some people.
[GASPS]
Wow.
He's so beautiful.
[INHALES]
[EXHALES]
I sense...
I sense my own.
And yet,
the one Knull seeks is not here.
Hmm.
What does he seek?
The black one.
Brock's symbiote?
He's the only one
who carries a codex.
The end is Knull.
You need your suit.
Still worried
about giving this thing a cold?
Venom carries the key
to Knull's freedom.
He must never obtain it.
Or your race will be killed.
You.
And you.
And...
you.
Everyone, everything.
How do we stop whatever's
up there from coming down here?
You can't.
He's older than the universe.
He needs the key.
Then everything will end.
How do we stop him
from getting it?
If the symbiote
and the host are alive,
then the codex is alive.
And if one of them dies?
The codex dies.
- Rex, you can't be serious.
- Oh, I'm game.
Destroying the codex
is the only way
it remains unobtainable. Right?
Hey, buddy, I'm talking to you.
Destroying it?
We have barely even
scratched the surface.
My people are dead.
Something is coming
that cannot be beaten.
I'm stopping
all this shit right now.
Science is sacrifice.
Teddy.
This is serious.
Listen to her.
[EXHALES]
Have you spoken
to your family recently?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
[INDISTINCT SINGING]
VENOM: I smell wet dog.
And sausamages!
Hey, friend-o.
You okay, there?
No, I'm not okay.
Uh...
It's pretty wild out there.
- I know.
- Yeah.
You hungry?
Yes.
MARTIN: Come over.
EDDIE: Thank you.
- So this is my wife, Nova Moon.
- NOVA: Hi.
And these are my kids.
Echo and Leaf.
- VENOM: A lifetime in therapy.
- EDDIE: Don't.
Huh?
Don't you dare! Wow.
How beautiful are your children.
And that's Blue.
[WHINES]
- Who is a...
- Dog.
And I'm Martin.
- Hey, Martin.
- Hey.
I'm Eddie.
- Nice to meet you, Eddie.
- You too. Pleasure.
- Come, sit, please. Come on.
- Okay. Thank you.
Jesus Christ.
So, right.
Oh.
So nothing died on that plate.
Namaste, man.
- Thank you.
- VENOM: Hard pass!
Oh, dear.
- Eddie, where you headed?
- New York.
Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Long way to New York
with naked shrimps, man.
[EDDIE LAUGHS] Yeah.
We could ride you out to Vegas.
Yeah.
VENOM: These people are weird,
I'm telling you.
That would be so kind.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Of course.
Life's one big adventure.
Who doesn't love
making new friends?
- Right?
This guy is so one of those
serial killer hitchhikers
from my favorite murder podcast.
- VENOM: Ha-ha!
- Baby. Not now.
How has social services
not taken us away yet?
[LAUGHS] She... She...
She's joking.
- I'm not.
- Please, honey.
[CHUCKLES]
So we're riding
the Extraterrestrial Highway.
- Yeah.
- The whatchamawhosit?
It's the road
that leads to Area 51.
See if we can spot us an alien
before they shut the place down
forever, you know?
It's, uh,
it's my lifelong dream.
VENOM: We could show him
right now!
Not a believer?
Actually, Martin...
[CLEARS THROAT]
How do I put this?
- I am.
- Oh.
Actually, I am a big,
big believer.
- VENOM: You're not that big.
- Oh, you a comedian now?
No, actually, I was in IT.
- Were you?
- Yeah.
- That's so cool.
- Oh, thanks.
I hope you don't get
disappointed, you know?
And I hope that if you
do find one, I hope you meet...
a really good alien, not a...
not a bad...
one.
- Yeah.
Well...
I know a dark force
when I see one, Eddie.
EDDIE: It's kinda hot in here.
Oh, you'll get used to it.
AC's really bad
for your health, you know.
[MARTIN STRUMMING GUITAR]
All right. Family ready?
- Yup.
- MARTIN: Guest ready?
Let's rock this camper.
♪ Ground control to Major Tom ♪
VENOM: Oh, I love a singalong!
Shoot me in the face.
♪ Take your protein pills
and put your helmet on ♪
VENOM: Oh, yeah!
- This is my jam!
- Ten...
...nine...
VENOM: ...eight, seven, six...
♪ Commencing countdown,
engines on ♪
...five, four...
...three, two, one
♪ Check ignition
and may God's love be with you ♪
- VENOM: Liftoff
- [LEAF SCREAMS]
- Come on, Eddie, sing along!
- I'm good, thanks.
You know the words!
Just think of this
as the tour bus.
We're the band,
and you can be the groupie.
VENOM: Come on! Don't be square.
Don't get me started.
[FAMILY, VENOM SING] ♪ This is
Major Tom to ground control ♪
♪ I'm stepping
through the door ♪
♪ And I'm floating
in a most peculiar way ♪
VENOM: Cheer up!
[ALL CONTINUE] ♪ And the stars
look very different today ♪
Why?
- ♪ For here am I ♪
- Why is this happening?
- ♪ Sitting in a tin can ♪
- VENOM: Can made of tin!
♪ Far above the world ♪
Like a bathtub, Eddie.
♪ Planet Earth is blue ♪
♪ And there's nothing I can do ♪
♪ This is ground control
to Major Tom ♪
VENOM: Sometimes
I think we would
have been happier
with a life like this.
♪ And the papers want to know
whose shirts you wear ♪
VENOM: You know?
Yep.
♪ Now it's time
to leave the capsule... ♪
- I know.
- ♪ ...if you dare ♪
VENOM: [SINGS] ♪ This is
Major Tom to ground control ♪
♪ I'm stepping
through the door ♪
♪ And I'm floating
in a most peculiar way ♪
♪ And the stars look
very different today ♪
[FADED] ♪ For here am I
sitting in a tin can ♪
♪ Far above the world ♪
You like chocolate?
Shh.
They don't let us eat sugar.
[WHISPERS] They don't?
EDDIE: I have a friend
who loves chocolate. Thank you.
It's very kind of you.
LEAF: I don't wanna
see an alien.
You don't?
It's scary.
Okay.
Well, you know,
it's okay to be scared.
I'm scared, like...
like, all the time.
Promise I won't see one?
Buddy.
[WHISPERS] Aliens are not real.
Okay?
I promise.
VENOM: You said the right thing.
You would make a good dad.
We've come a long way,
you and me.
We have many more roads
to travel, buddy.
VENOM: Wouldn't that be nice?
You say something?
Mm? No. Just dreaming, I guess.
Hm.
That's the Nierika.
"Nierika"?
Yeah.
There's a doorway in our minds
that usually remains
hidden and secret
until the time of death.
Crazy things
in this world, Eddie.
You can see 'em
if you're open.
Oh, I seen them.
Hm.
VENOM: I'm glad we didn't
eat this fine family.
["WILD WORLD"
BY CAT STEVENS PLAYING]
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
la, la-la, la ♪
♪ Now that I've lost
everything to you ♪
♪ You say you want to start
something new ♪
♪ And it's breaking my heart
you're leaving ♪
♪ Baby, I'm grieving ♪
♪ But if you want to leave,
take good care... ♪
Welcome to the city
of second chances.
LEAF: Woah!
♪ Ooh, baby, baby
it's a wild world ♪
[FADING] ♪ It's hard to get by
just upon a smile... ♪
Thank you, thank you.
Take care, buddy. Thank you.
Stay, Blue. Stay.
Thank you. Take care, Blue.
Vegas.
Listen, I just want you
to have this.
- Please. And...
- Oh, Martin, that's a lot of--
- Thank you.
- Quality support cushioning.
Plus, they come with
an antimicrobial footbed.
VENOM: No! Reject them.
Worse than Crocs.
Thank you.
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
it's a wild world ♪
♪ But I'll always remember you ♪
Goodbye, Martin.
It's goodbye for now.
That's what I like to think,
Eddie.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Martin.
You know that doorway...
The Nierika?
Yeah. It's open.
All right? Just...
Be safe.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, Jesus.
Well, this is an all-time low.
[SHOWGIRLS LAUGH]
[HORN HONKS]
VENOM: You have chocolate!
Mm!
- VENOM: Yum!
- [GROANS SOFTLY]
I would like to see her
when we get to New York, Eddie.
You know, she was built
to welcome visitors
to America, buddy.
And that's you.
VENOM: You think so, Eddie?
Oh, yeah. I know so.
When we get out of this mess,
we'll go see her.
We'll say, "Hi, Lady Liberty."
VENOM: And see a Broadway show!
Yeah, sure.
VENOM: Wow!
I know how much
you hate musicals.
Yeah, it's gonna be great.
VENOM: What's next, Thelma?
Well, Louise,
I'm not sure 20 bucks
is gonna get us much
in the way of a motor transport.
And I'm not ever riding
an alien horse again.
So I guess it looks like
we're stealing cars.
VENOM: No,
I've watched Rain Man,
and in my infinite wisdom
as a celestial being,
- working the system is easy.
- Uh...
VENOM: We hit the slots,
then blackjack, then roulette!
Bingo-bango!
Luxury ride,
Bluetooth sound system, AC
and the top down.
Because that's how we roll.
Paris Casino
has a strict dress code.
No, you know what? It's a hotel.
These are my vacation clothes.
BOUNCER: Get better ones.
VENOM: He's not wrong.
Look at you.
Don't push it, all right, buddy?
- VENOM: Want a hand?
- [SIGHS] Yes.
- [BOUNCER GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
I didn't mean knock him out.
What are you doing?
- VENOM: He was being a dick.
- Yeah, but...
VENOM: Oh! Look.
We need a disguise.
[WHISPERS] What are we doing?
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
Hi.
- [MAN CHUCKLES]
- [URINE SPLASHING]
EDDIE: Oh God.
VENOM: Warm.
[GRUNTS]
Why do you keep
knocking people out?
What is wrong with you?
Jesus, why?
So sorry, buddy.
I am so, so sorry.
VENOM: Eddie! Yeah, baby.
Now no one will recognize us.
- Seriously.
- [SIGHS]
You could get voted
People's Sexiest Man of the Year
if anyone cared
who you were anymore.
I've won
Sexy Man awards before.
VENOM: 'Course you have.
- EDDIE: Hey. Hey.
- MAN: Yeah?
The guy that did that?
I saw it.
He's in the arch over there.
- He's shitfaced.
- OFFICER: All right.
We are bad people.
VENOM: Yeah, we are!
We're keeping these shoes,
by the way.
VENOM: We are so money,
and we know it!
Welcome to the Paris.
- EDDIE: Thank you.
- No, thank you.
- Just sit on the ground.
- What happened?
["HARD TO HANDLE"
BY OTIS REDDING PLAYING]
♪ Baby, here I am
I'm a man on the scene ♪
♪ I can give you
what you want ♪
♪ But you got to go home
with me ♪
♪ I've got some
good ol' loving ♪
- [SLOT MACHINE CHIMING]
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
VENOM: Oh, yes!
Let me multiply that 20.
Let me quadruplify it.
EDDIE: What are you doing?
No. This is all the money
that we have.
VENOM:
♪ Luck, be a lady tonight ♪
No.
[LOSING SLOT MACHINE SOUND]
VENOM: Smashing jacket!
Let's eat him and steal it!
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
VENOM: I know Lady Luck
is on our side tonight!
No, I would say that Lady Luck
is definitely
not on your side tonight.
In fact, I would even
go so far to say
that Lady Luck hates you, buddy.
- VENOM: I can't stop now!
- Of course you can't stop.
VENOM: What is this feeling?
- It's like: Aaah!
- This feeling?
VENOM: It's like all
of my problems have gone away!
Do this all the time!
[LOSING SLOT MACHINE SOUND]
VENOM: Eddie.
I need more money.
But we don't have
any more money, buddy.
VENOM: Goddamn it!
[GLASS BREAKING]
EDDIE: You are a sore loser.
- VENOM: You're a sore loser!
- Oh...
[GROANS]
I think you broke my foot.
VENOM: Ah!
Lady Luck is a fickle slut!
We should have played
that machine!
[WOMAN 1 CHEERING]
No effing way.
Eddie Brock?
- Mrs. Chen! That's not yours.
- [WOMAN 2 GASPS]
- I'm sorry.
- VENOM: Eddie! It's Mrs. Chen!
- Oh, Mrs. Chen!
- [MRS. CHEN SCREAMING]
Eddie, baby!
EDDIE: Mrs. Chen!
Mrs. Chen! Mrs. Chen!
- VENOM: I'm gonna cry.
- Me too.
[GASPS]
Wow. What happened to you?
You look hot!
- So do you.
- VENOM: Really hot.
- I always look hot.
- Yeah.
- Is the big guy in there?
Do you like my dress?
I've been winning so big,
they gave me
a credit line
at the clothes store.
And then the penthouse suite!
Wow. You know I stole this suit
off a guy who pissed on me.
I knocked him out.
I left him in a bush.
Well, that explains the stink.
You could use my room
to clean up, and then we party.
Oh, that would be so good.
And room service.
Oh, yes!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
We got him.
Positive ID on Brock.
CCTV hit,
the Paris Hotel, Vegas.
- Have we reconstituted The Six?
- Yes, sir.
Put 'em in.
- [BEEPS]
- The Six are en route.
They'll bring him in.
At this time, I'm requesting
control of the Imperium Program.
MAN:
You have my permission, general.
[RUMBLING]
BOY: When thunder roars,
head indoors.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO]
[LOW GROWLING]
Let's dance, baby.
- No. No.
- VENOM: Yeah! I love dancing!
Are you crazy?
That thing will find us.
Don't be a party pooper.
No! Do not encourage him.
You know what, Mrs. Chen?
We are fugitives.
We are on the run.
So, thank you for having us.
We gotta go.
- VENOM: You're no fun!
- [SIGHS]
One last dance before you go.
VENOM: We never do anything
- I want to do.
- What?
Just a little dance.
VENOM: And you gave away
my chickens.
Yeah!
[GROWLING]
[CODEX PULSING]
Let's cut a rug, Mrs. Chen.
EDDIE: I give up.
["DANCING QUEEN"
BY ABBA PLAYING]
Uh-huh.
Ha! Ooh.
Ha! Hmm!
Uh-huh.
EDDIE: Oh, no,
I cannot unsee that.
I cannot unsee that!
[VENOM SINGING]
♪ You can dance ♪
♪ You can dan... ♪
♪ Having the time of our lives ♪
[MUSIC SPEEDS UP]
♪ See that girl ♪
♪ Watch that scene
diggin' the dancing queen ♪
EDDIE: When did you two
practice this?
[XENOPHAGE SHRIEKING]
[GROWLS]
♪ Where they play
the right music ♪
♪ Getting in the swing... ♪
[SONG FADES]
- Goddamnit!
- [GASPS]
EDDIE: I told you
this would happen!
- [CODEX PULSING]
- [MRS. CHEN SCREAMS]
VENOM: Don't panic.
She can't see the codex.
MRS. CHEN:
What the hell is that?
Wow. So ugly!
[SHRIEKS]
Stay very calm.
She can't see the thing
she's looking for.
- [GROWLS]
- MRS. CHEN: Ah!
[WHIMPERS]
[GROWLS]
[HELICOPTER HOVERING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO]
SOLDIER: Go, go, go!
- [EDDIE GRUNTS]
- [MRS. CHEN SCREAMING]
- [GROANS]
- [VENOM SCREECHES]
[GROANS]
- [ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
- [HIGH PITCHED GROAN]
Target acquired.
- You leave Eddie alone!
- SOLDIER 1: Silence!
My shoes.
SOLDIER 2: Go.
Move out, move out!
[GROWLS]
[LOW GROWLING]
MARTIN: Wow.
[CHUCKLES]
Area 51.
- Yeah.
- Huh?
Yeah.
We made it.
ECHO:
You finally got to see it, Dad.
It's kind of cool...
I guess.
Yeah.
NOVA: Leaf.
Where you goin', hon?
Well, let's see
if we can't find us
something cooler. Come on.
Come on, guys.
NOVA: Okay, babe.
Lifelong dream.
All right. Go, go, go, go, go!
I smell alien.
[NOVA LAUGHS]
[WHIMPERS]
[VENOM, LOW SHRIEKING]
He's deteriorating
without his host.
Poor thing.
Put him below with the others.
Safer there.
[SHRIEKS]
[VENOM, LOW SHRIEKING]
[MARTIN WHISPERS] Down, down.
Come on, come on.
All right.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think we're gonna get
a better view from up there.
[PANTING]
Follow me, guys. Come on.
This is so exciting.
I can't believe we're here.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow.
Wow. Oh, wow.
What is this?
It's all broken.
So sad.
[GROANS]
Buddy?
Hey, buddy?
Oh no.
Oh... [GROANS]
No.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, my God, how many hangovers
can you have in one day?
MULLIGAN: Eddie?
Hello?
They did this to me.
Mulligan?
Why?
You're alive?
What are you doing here?
[SQUELCHING]
We're being hunted, Eddie.
You have what he needs.
Protect the codex
from dark hands.
A symbiote army waits here.
Free them.
Protect it, Eddie.
Knull...
must stay locked away.
[DOOR OPENS]
Eddie, I'm Dr. Paine.
Where's my friend?
He's safe for now.
[DOOR OPENS]
Great news!
- Oh shit.
- We're all done here.
All of this
is out of your hands.
This is my lab.
No, no, not yours.
You just work here.
Or you did.
You, Christmas,
you're going home.
And what about them?
- You heard what it said.
- Hands up.
The codex only exists
if they're both alive.
Yeah, we're good. We're good.
You killed one of my people.
I'm returning the favor
personally. Please escort
- Dr. Paine out of here.
- No.
- Don't move.
- Christmas!
Time to go.
- Hey!
- [WARBLING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
Big mistake.
- Fire!
- Run!
- [GASPS]
- [GROWLS]
[CODEX PULSING]
[YELLS]
- Oh my God!
- SOLDIER: Fall back, fall back!
- Go!
- [ROARS]
[SNARLS]
[ROARS]
- Venom, run. Go!
- [SCREECHES]
[TOXIN GRUNTING]
Let's go! Move! Clear! Clear!
Release the symbiotes!
- SOLDIER: Go! Go!
- [BOTH PANTING]
- [XENOPHAGE SHRIEKING]
- [WOMAN SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
- Come on.
- Go! Go!
Hurry up! Move!
Get back!
Ah!
Jim!
[GROWLS]
- [SHRIEKS]
- [GASPS]
- [ROARING]
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[SYMBIOTE GROWLS]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[CACKLES]
Let's go.
Take her down.
[SHRIEKING]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
[GROWLS]
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARING]
[SHRIEKS]
Ah! [GROANS]
[XENOPHAGE SCREECHING]
Come on!
[SNARLS]
[GASPS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Get the codex out of here.
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [XENOPHAGE SCREECHING]
EDDIE: That's our way out.
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[CODEX PULSING]
[ROARS]
VENOM: You,
break us out of here!
[SIGHS]
- There's no aliens here, kids.
- Hmm.
- [EXPLOSION]
- [GASPS]
[SYMBIOTES SNARLING]
VENOM: Best shoes ever!
Whoa! What was that?
- [SOLDIERS SHOUTING]
- [SHRIEKING]
[GRUNTS]
- [PANTING] Okay.
- SOLDIER: We gotta go! Move it!
- [GRUNTS]
- [XENOPHAGE SHRIEKS]
We are leaving!
Move!
Move, move!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- Dad.
- MARTIN: It's all right, kids.
- [XENOPHAGE SHRIEKING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
Aliens! Alien invasion!
Alien attack!
[ROARS]
Motherfucker!
[DR. PAINE GASPS]
[SNARLS]
- You two, get airborne!
- SOLDIER: Right away, sir!
On me!
Hurry up, airborne! Move, move,
move! In the Hummers! Go!
VENOM:
We've got to get the codex
as far away as possible.
[XENOPHAGE GROWLING]
- It's Eddie?
- BOTH: It's Eddie.
- Eddie! Hey!
- NOVA: Eddie!
- Oh, no.
- Eddie, Eddie!
Martin. And family.
[PANTING]
You can't be here, Martin.
Dark forces, man.
[SYMBIOTES AND XENOPHAGE
GROWLING]
[XENOPHAGE SHRIEKING]
Eddie, can you help us?
I lied. Aliens are real.
My best friend
in the whole world is one.
He's gonna get you
out of here, okay?
Okay.
- Don't... Don't be scared.
- Hi.
Wow.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Thanks for the chocolate.
- You're welcome.
- [XENOPHAGE SHRIEKING]
Ah! [SNARLS]
No!
Mom, Dad!
[LEAF SCREAMING]
Dad!
Hold on, kids!
[CRYING]
MARTIN: Hold on, kids!
[ALL SCREAMING]
Eddie!
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
He was trying to protect you.
We are not the bad guys!
MARTIN: Echo! Leaf.
- My baby, my baby.
- Mom!
- Thank you, Eddie.
- You're welcome.
[GROANING]
You gotta be kidding me.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS] Get in!
MARTIN: Run. Run.
Run!
LEAF: Eddie!
[WARBLING]
[VENOM GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Go. Bring me that codex.
[CHITTERS AND GROWLS]
[GRUNTS]
What's that noise?
VENOM: She phoned home.
[WHOOSHES]
Oh shit.
- [GROWLING]
- [SCREAMING]
[SNARLS]
[SHRIEKING]
- NOVA: Jesus!
- Get down! Get down! Get under!
Take cover! Take cover!
I got you.
[GROANING]
VENOM: She saved us.
There's only one thing
that's gonna distract them.
VENOM: Copy.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
- Get 'em back to their van!
- What?
Come on! Hurry, hurry!
I'm gonna round them up.
Have the chopper follow me.
- Go, go, go! Go!
- [LEAF SCREAMS]
[SYMBIOTE GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [ROARS]
[CODEX PULSING]
[XENOPHAGES GROWLING]
Go!
He's leading them to a kill box.
When you get a lock,
vaporize 'em!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS AND YELLS]
[GROWLS]
We're home. We're back.
Okay, okay. Hold it.
- LEAF: Run!
- Go, kids! Go! Come on!
- Hurry. Hurry, honey.
- [BARKS]
Thank you!
Aliens suck!
[BOTH GROWLING]
- Light 'em up!
- SOLDIER: Copy that.
Target eliminated.
- [GROWLING]
- [SOLDIER SCREAMING]
No! No!
Thompson down!
It's coming down. Go!
- [GROWLING]
- [SOLDIER SCREAMING]
- [SHRIEKS]
- [GRUNTS]
Slide!
[GRUNTS]
Oh sh--!
Oh! Go away!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
Let's finish this.
VENOM: With pleasure.
The chopper blades!
I got you.
- It's okay.
- Get him somewhere safe.
Oh God.
[PULSATING]
[EDDIE GRUNTS]
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
Okay. Okay.
[ROARS]
[SNARLS]
[GROWLS]
[YELLS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [PULSATING]
[GRUNTS]
No.
[REX GRUNTS]
DR. PAINE: Okay. Okay.
Still living
your brother's dream?
Oh, my God.
[XENOPHAGES ROARING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- I'm coming! I'm coming!
- LEAF: Dad, come on!
Dad! Dad! Run! Come on!
[GROANING]
- [DISTANT EXPLOSION]
- [EDDIE GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
I'm proud of you, Eddie.
You did it all yourself.
Well, some of it.
[GROANS]
[XENOPHAGES GROWLING]
- [DISTANT EXPLOSION]
- [GASPS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATH TREMBLING]
I really would have liked
to have seen her.
Who?
Lady Liberty.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, we're going.
We're gonna go just as soon
as we get...
out of here.
They're just going
to keep coming.
We'll never leave
this place, friend.
- [DISTANT EXPLOSION]
- [GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Okay, well...
I thought we were gonna be
the Lethal Protector.
We are.
That's what this is.
[DISTANT EXPLOSION]
Yeah.
All right.
[GRUNTS]
[XENOPHAGES GROWLING]
Come and get us.
[GRUNTING]
[LABORED BREATHING]
[ROARING]
- Go.
- Huh?
Go.
- DR. PAINE: Oh, my God.
- [BOTH PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[EDDIE GRUNTS]
What are you doin'?
I'll never forget you.
Don't forget me either, Eddie.
No.
Time to go.
[GRUNTS]
Strickland.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Strickland authorized.
[GROANING]
No.
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH PANTING]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
Strickland.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Strickland authorized.
[XENOPHAGES SCREECHING]
Oh?
Huh? Huh?
[PANTING]
It's just bye for now.
[GASPS]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
No.
No!
No! No!
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[SHRIEKING]
[GRUNTS]
Go!
[BOTH GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
No, Eddie!
[CRYING] Eddie!
Oh, my God.
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Nierika.
Hey, buddy.
I just had a crazy dream.
Buddy?
OFFICER: He's not coming back.
But I need him back.
OFFICER:
He wasn't meant for this place.
You couldn't have kept him...
and he couldn't have kept you.
For your bravery,
you both have the heartfelt
thanks of a grateful nation.
Eddie, you're free
to start your life again.
Everything that happened
in San Francisco
and in the last few days...
consider it expunged.
Just so you're clear,
of course...
you ever breathe a word of this
to any living soul
you will spend
the rest of that life
in the coldest,
darkest hole imaginable.
Good luck, Eddie.
[DOOR CLOSES]
["MEMORIES" BY MAROON 5 PLAYING]
♪ Here's to the ones
that we got ♪
♪ Cheers to the wish
you were here, but you're not ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ Of everything
we've been through ♪
♪ Toast to the ones
here today ♪
that we lost on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ And the memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
♪ There's a time
that I remember ♪
♪ When I did not know no pain ♪
♪ When I believed in forever ♪
♪ Everything would
stay the same ♪
♪ Now my heart
feel like December ♪
♪ When somebody say your name ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't reach out
to call you ♪
♪ But I know I will
one day, yeah ♪
♪ Everybody hurts sometimes ♪
♪ Everybody hurts someday,
ay, ay ♪
♪ But everything gon' be
all right ♪
♪ Go and raise a glass
and say, ay ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that we got ♪
♪ Cheers to the wish
you were here, but you're not ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ Of everything
we've been through ♪
♪ Toast to the ones
here today ♪
that we lost on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ And the memories bring back,
memories bring back you... ♪
I won't forget you, buddy.
♪ Memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
[SONG ENDS]
["ONE LAST DANCE" BY TOM MORELLO
AND GRANDSON PLAYING]
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Push me into overdrive
what a lovely way to die ♪
♪ If you're with me by my side
I'm in for the ride ♪
♪ There's no running
no escape ♪
♪ All the venom never waits ♪
♪ Once you feel it hit
your veins, it's too late ♪
♪ You're gone ♪
♪ And there's no stopping
or slowing down ♪
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Push me up against the wall
it's the final curtain call ♪
♪ 'Bout to be
a barroom brawl, oh ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ There's no stopping
or slowing down ♪
♪ There won't be
a next time now ♪
♪ But I'll be fine
if you're around ♪
♪ Give me one last dance ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ There's no stopping
what's going down ♪
♪ There won't be
a next time now ♪
♪ But I'll be fine
if you're around ♪
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ♪
♪ Ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the
before we hit the ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
[SONG ENDS]
KNULL: Your champion has fallen.
[VOICE ECHOING]
The planets will be mine.
The King in Black is awake.
I will kill your world.
Everyone will burn.
And you...
will watch.
["I HAD SOME HELP" BY POST
MALONE AND MORGAN WALLEN PLAYS]
♪ You got a lotta nerve
don't you, baby? ♪
♪ I only hit the curb
'cause you made me ♪
♪ You're telling all
your friends that I'm crazy ♪
♪ Like I'm the only one ♪
♪ Why'd you throw
them stones if you ♪
♪ Had a wild hair
of your own or two? ♪
♪ Living in your big
glass house with a view ♪
♪ I thought you knew ♪
♪ I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ You thought I'd take
the blame for us a-crumbling ♪
♪ Go round like
you ain't guilty of something ♪
♪ Already lost the game
that you been running ♪
♪ Guess it's catching up
to you, huh ♪
♪ You think that
you're so innocent ♪
♪ After all the shit you did ♪
♪ I ain't an angel
you ain't heaven-sent ♪
♪ Can't wash our hands
of this ♪
♪ I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ It takes two
to break a heart in two ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Baby, you blame me
and, baby, I blame you ♪
♪ Aw, if that ain't the truth ♪
♪ Oh, I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
[SONG ENDS]
["2FACE" BY IAN PLAYING]
[DISTORTED]
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there
and it's getting harder to ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there
and it's ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there ♪
♪ And it's getting harder
to fight this feeling, so ♪
♪ Come and find out with me ♪
♪ Before it's turned
upside down right before us ♪
♪ And that's okay
if you miss me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm-a make sure
that door stay wide open ♪
♪ For you and me, baby ♪
♪ We just on
a different team, but ♪
♪ That's okay with me 'cause ♪
♪ You remind me of
my favorite things ever ♪
♪ Let me cut out the nonsense ♪
♪ Hundred for the bag, another
hundred for the contents ♪
♪ This life ... a contest, and
if you think you first place ♪
♪ Get your thoughts checked ♪
♪ You just can't grasp
the concept of ♪
♪ Something that's
beyond yourself ♪
♪ This could be
our last dance ♪
♪ And I need
the best way through it ♪
♪ Won't nobody be there
to tell you direction ♪
♪ When ... get hectic
and stressful ♪
♪ It's pressing that I get
past this, but I can't ♪
♪ I just can't do it ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ But all your friends
going right down with you ♪
♪ You think I'd really pay
the price that simple? ♪
♪ I ain't never gonna flip and
they don't like that 'bout me ♪
♪ We got nobody watching,
take it off for me, shorty ♪
♪ Just give me this ♪
♪ And I could give it all
to you, shorty ♪
♪ I just want to know
if you would ♪
♪ Give your all to me, shorty ♪
♪ 'Cause you're all
that I got ♪
♪ If I'm honest about it ♪
♪ You couldn't have picked
a worse time for this ♪
♪ I just wasted ten times
what you earn ♪
♪ We just can't be
getting high every day ♪
♪ I guess I should've never
tried from the jump ♪
♪ I'm fried than a ♪
♪ Outside, head high
than a ♪
♪ I got to catch a red-eye
for a club showing ♪
♪ Boy, I'm 'bout to sit my
down and get a dub for it ♪
♪ You just can't grasp
the concept of ♪
♪ Something that's
beyond yourself ♪
♪ This could be
our last dance ♪
♪ And I need the best way
through it ♪
♪ Won't nobody be there
to tell you direction ♪
♪ When ... get hectic
and stressful ♪
♪ It's pressing that I'll get
past this, but I can't ♪
♪ I just can't do it ♪
♪ I just can't do it. ♪
[SONG ENDS]
["KNULL & VOID" BY CZARFACE,
FRANKIE PULITZER & METHOD MAN]
♪ Czarface ♪
♪ What a mind trick
enough to make my mind sick ♪
♪ And eyes twitch
I'm ticked off ♪
♪ The shift is seismic ♪
♪ Everything I thought I knew
is Knull & Void ♪
♪ And destroyed, day is night
left is right ♪
♪ Heavy's light
black is white ♪
♪ War is peace, peace is war
either or ♪
♪ You woke up down 20, you
should've been keeping score ♪
♪ A fallacy
it rattles me to my core ♪
♪ Of the Earth, it's reversed
what is worse? ♪
♪ You could call this a curse ♪
♪ There are new ways to die ♪
♪ And I am anti
polar opposite ♪
♪ Stand by
you were told a damn lie ♪
♪ Trying to be transparent
and see-through ♪
♪ In an opaque world
could eat you ♪
♪ Death has no manners when it
greets you, what I teach you ♪
♪ Put that contract
with world peace in the trash ♪
♪ I could be a free agent
with Venom in the flask ♪
♪ At last ♪
♪ Take off the mask ♪
♪ Take off the mask
slow news day ♪
♪ The drama queen
says hysteria, pandemonia ♪
♪ Is outlined
with fierce fires ♪
♪ All around the border
there's clear lines drawn ♪
♪ All barrels pointed
35 degrees ♪
♪ Skies torn
filled with satellites ♪
♪ Pixel features formed
coded ♪
♪ Interior mind loaded
image uploading ♪
♪ Conspiracists pictured this
foreboding ♪
♪ Analytics from the armchair
predicted years before ♪
♪ Pored over
spoken too much over the Net ♪
♪ Reeling from the residue
of gun smoke ♪
♪ And even though
the guns smoking ♪
♪ If the horse already bolted ♪
♪ Then the barn door
is wide open ♪
♪ Things ain't always
what it seems ♪
♪ And these things
seem the same ♪
♪ But that ain't always
what it means ♪
♪ What is real, what is dream
the public eye is seldom seen ♪
♪ Seldom heard
the learning curve ♪
♪ Is sell your soul
to sell a scene ♪
♪ Spread the word
let it breathe ♪
♪ Plant the seed
let it breed ♪
♪ Tell your dawgs to tell
your G's, then tell it all ♪
♪ If I'm cut, let it bleed ♪
♪ If it ain't broke
then let it be ♪
♪ Tell my loved ones
I'd rather let 'em go ♪
♪ Than let 'em grieve ♪
♪ Too much pride
to let it leave ♪
♪ Can't see the forest
for the trees ♪
♪ Feel the darkness
setting in ♪
♪ Just let it in
and set it free ♪
♪ I'm better off a better me
I bet it costs to be a boss ♪
♪ I'm like of course
it better be ♪
♪ You take a loss
you better see ♪
♪ My point of view
is not to view ♪
♪ But make a point
to point at you ♪
♪ Then make a point
to prove a point ♪
♪ To make it
just as pointless, too ♪
♪ Oh, silly me, I'm just
as vain as this soliloquy ♪
♪ You feeling me,
then I'm the perfect ending ♪
♪ To this trilogy ♪
[SONG ENDS]
- [MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WIND BLOWING]
Hello? Hello?
¿Hola? Hello?
[YELLS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]